Inventory of the William J. Casey papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- MEMORABILIA (Boxes 625-636)
  - Certificate of appointment as alternate governor of the Asian Development Bank, 1973 (Box 634)
  - Certificate of appointment as alternate governor of the International Bank for Reconstruction and Development, 1973 (Box 634)
  - Certificate of appointment as member of the Commission on Organization of the Government for the Conduct of Foreign Policy, 1973 (Box 634)
  - Sky Island Club certificate, 1973 (Box 634)
  - Certificate of appointment as Under Secretary of State for Economic Affairs, 1973 (Box 634)
  - Richard M. Nixon and Spiro Agnew presidential and vice presidential inaugural souvenir, 1973 (Box 625)
  - Letters of congratulation by Gerald R. Ford and Nelson A. Rockefeller for receipt of Veterans of the O.S.S. William J. Donovan Award, 1974 (Box 627)
  - Certificate of appointment as president and chairman of the Export-Import Bank of the United States, 1974 (Box 634)
  - Veterans of the O.S.S. William J. Donovan Award, 1974 (Box 628)
  - White House Fellows certificate, 1975 (Box 628)
  - Letter by Gerald R. Ford upon resignation as President and Chairman of the Export-Import Bank, 1975 (Box 628)
  - Certificate of appointment as member of the President's Foreign Intelligence Advisory Board, 1976 (Box 634)
  - Long Island Board of Realtors certificate, 1978 (Box 625)
  - Honorary degree, Adelphi University, 1979 (Box 625)
  - Honorary degree, Molloy College, 1979 (Box 625)
  - Philippines cartoon, 1980s (Box 627)
  - Plaque, apparently associated with Afghan guerrillas, 1980s (Box 627)
  - Newspaper headlines of Ronald Reagan presidential election, 1980 (Box 634)
  - Reagan/Bush Campaign and Presidential Transition Team identification badges, 1980-1981 (Box 631)
  - Presidential Transition Team certificate, 1981 (Box 627)
  - Presidential inauguration license plates, 1981 (Box 626)
  - Certificate of appointment as Director of Central Intelligence, 1981 (Box 634)
  - Cartoon of WJC as Director of Central Intelligence, 1980s (Box 634)
  - Honorary degree and fellowship certificates, Polytechnic Institute of New York, 1981 (Box 628)
  - Honorary award, St. John's University, 1981 (Box 625)
  - Honorary degree, Polytechnic Institute of New York, 1981 (Box 625)
  - Long Island Lighting Company resolutions, 1981 (Box 625)
  - North American Air Defense Command plaque, 1982 (Box 629)
  - Dutch resistance medal, 1982 (Box 631)
  - Lessons-Learned Seminar certificate, 1982 (Box 633)
  - Distinguished Intelligence Medal citations, 1983 and 1987 (Box 628)
  - William J. Donovan Memorial Foundation plaque, 1984 (Box 629)
  - Honorary degree, Long Island University, 1986 (Box 628)
  - Oversize memorabilia item relating to Angola, 1986 (Box 636)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission resolution, 1987 (Box 625)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission memorial certificate (Box 628)
  - Jack Kemp Congressional Record tribute, 1987 (Box 633)
  - Christendom College memorial items, 1988 (Box 625, 633)
  - Tribute from Richard M. Nixon, undated (Box 634)
  - Long Island Association of Commerce and Industry poster, undated (Box 629)
  - Junior Chamber of Commerce award (Box 628)
  - Award, apparently Lebanese (Box 625)
  - Oversize memorabilia item, apparently Kuwaiti (Box 635)
  - Oversize engraved plates (two) (Box 630)
  - Miscellany (Box 628, 631, 633)
  - Center for the Study of the Presidency award to Sophia Casey, 1991 (Box 633)
- DECLASSIFIED RECORDS, 1943-1986
  Formerly security-classified records of the U.S. government, released in full or in part. Arranged chronologically by date of release by Hoover, thereunder by title and in chronological order by date of creation.
  - 2012 February release of records, 1943-1986; 106.0 digital files (Reading room Workstation)
    The bulk relate to Casey's service in the Office of Strategic Services, Department of State, and Central Intelligence Agency. Available as PDF files.
  - 2015 July release of records, 1944 (Box-folder 602: 8)
    Photocopies of three maps of the low countries and France titled "12th Monthly Progress Repot to S.H.A.E.F.," featuring liberated areas as of 21 August 1944 (Map A-1), 25 August 1944 (Map A-2), and 4 September 1944 (Map A-3).
  - 2017 release of records, 1941-1986 (Reading room Workstation)